(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-28T17:09:00.494064",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ダメダメよ☆
Don't do that☆
右から左へと言葉が流れる
Words flow from right to left on the screen,
退屈そうな顔 画面見つめる君
And you look bored, staring at the screen.
次元の壁越えていつでも逢いに行く
I'll cross dimensions to see you anytime.
心の準備をちゃんとしておいてね
Make sure you're ready in your heart, okay?
君のこと誰よりも分かっているだから私に任せて
I know you better than anyone, so leave it to me!
怖がらないで二人で踊りましょう
Don't be scared, let's dance together.
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
はじけるリズムに合わせて
Groove to the popping rhythm,
嫌なこと何から何まで全部忘れて
Forget all the bad things and live it up!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
私はここに居るから
Because I am right here,
少しでも視線を逸らしちゃダメダメよ☆
Don't take your eyes off me even for a second☆
重くて見えない日 兄貴に釣られた日
When it's too heavy to see, when you're hooked by big bro,
心で呼んでみて すぐに飛んで行くわ
Call me from your heart and I'll fly right to you!
授業では教えないことを君に教えてあげるわ
I'll teach you things they never teach in school.
夜の扉を二人で開きましょう
Let's open the gates to the night together!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
あふれる想いはFor you
My overflowing feelings are all for you.
限りあるこの時を胸に刻んで
Engrave this limited time in your heart.
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
朝日が昇ればサヨナラ
When the morning sun rises, it's goodbye.
寂しそうなそんな目 されてもダメだから
Even if you give me that lonely look, no way!
君のこと誰よりも分かっている
I know you better than anyone,
だから全てを晒して
So reveal everything to me,
生まれた意味を二人で見つけましょう
And let's find the meaning of birth together!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
高まる鼓動を感じて
Feel your heartbeat growing stronger,
さあ覚悟できたらこの手をとって
Now, if you're ready, take my hand!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
輝く君が好きなの
I love you when you're shining bright,
全力で飛び出そう 用意はいいかしら？
Let's jump out with all our might. Ready?
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
はじけるリズムに合わせて
Groove to the popping rhythm,
嫌なこと何から何まで全部忘れて
Forget all the bad things and live it up!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
私はここに居るから
Because I am right here,
少しでも視線を逸らしちゃダメダメよ☆
Don't take your eyes off me even for a second☆
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
朝日が昇ればサヨナラ
When the morning sun rises, it's goodbye.
寂しそうなそんな目 されてもダメだから
Even if you give me that lonely look, no way!
私を捕まえて
Catch me!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
君のこと誰よりも分かっている
I know you better than anyone,
だから全てをさらして
So reveal everything to me,
生まれた意味を二人で見つけましょう
And let's find the meaning of birth together!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
高まる鼓動を感じて
Feel your heartbeat growing stronger,
さあ覚悟できたらこの手をとって
Now, if you're ready, take my hand!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
輝く君が好きなの
I love you when you're shining bright,
全力で飛び出そう 用意はいいかしら？
Let's jump out with all our might. Ready?
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
はじけるリズムに合わせて
Groove to the popping rhythm,
嫌なこと何から何まで全部忘れて
Forget all the bad things and live it up!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
私はここに居るから
Because I am right here,
少しでも視線を逸らしちゃダメダメよ☆
Don't take your eyes off me even for a second☆
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
はじけるリズムに合わせて
Groove to the popping rhythm,
嫌なこと何から何まで全部忘れて
Forget all the bad things and live it up!
ルカルカ☆ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka☆ Night Fever!
私はここに居るから
Because I am right here,
少しでも視線を逸らしちゃダメダメよ☆
Don't take your eyes off me even for a second☆
ダメダメよ☆
No, no, no!
ルカルカ★ナイトフィーバー
Luka Luka Night Fever
私はここにいるから
I'll be right here,
少しでも視線をそらしちゃ
so don't look away even a little bit—
ダメダメよ☆
no, no, no!
No, no, no!
はーい、みんなー！
Hi everyone!
おるおるおー！
Hello, hello!
突然音が始まったからもうびっくりしちゃったのよー！
The music started all of a sudden, so it totally surprised me!
本番が始まるまで油断してまったりしてたのらよー（笑）
I was just chilling and letting my guard down before the show started!
ということで、本日
So, today—
2022年7月4日は、ルーナの活動2周年記念日なのだよー！
July 4th, 2022, is Luna's 2nd anniversary!
見に来てくれてありがとうなのだよー！
Thank you so much for coming to watch!
みんなのおかげで今日という素敵な日を迎えられたなのだよー！
Thanks to everyone, I was able to welcome such a wonderful day today!
おる、あおるおる、みんなおるで！おう、ありがとうな、ありがとう、みんな来てくれてありがとうー！
Or, ao oru oru, everyone's here! Thank you everyone for coming!
えーと、あ、まず今日、こちらね、姫森ルーナ2周年記念ライブで、スイートね、いっぱいしてくださいー！
Um, first, today, for Himemori Luna's 2nd anniversary live, please send lots of sweets!
そして、今日ね、最後にね、すごい、すごい重大発表があるのよー！
And also, today, at the very end, there's a huge major announcement!
最後まで見ていってねー！
Be sure to watch until the very end!
ぴんぽーん、ぴんぽーん…うるせー！うるせーな！
Ding-dong, ding-dong... Shut up! Shut up!
うるせーんだよ！
Shut up!
ガチャガチャガチャ、開けて！ルーナ寝てるんじゃない？
Jiggle, open it! Isn't Luna sleeping?
いややっぱ眠たそうだからね、この子、ちょっと待って、壊すから、ちょっと待って！
No, she looks sleepy—wait, you'll break it, wait!
ルーナ大丈夫！？生きてるかー！？
Luna, are you okay?! Are you alive?!
あー！記憶どこから？どこから！？
Ah! Where did my memory start? From where?!
どうしたの？何何何？
What happened? What, what, what?
えーだっていきてるじゃん！
Eh, you're alive!
生きてるけどさ、寝てただけね！
I'm alive, I was just sleeping!
寝てなかったし！起きてたし！
I wasn't sleeping! I was awake!
あ、あろーな！きろーぜんたーるです！あろーろぼくでよー！
Ah, aloha! It's Aki Rosenthal! Alo, I'm Roboco!
え、何何何、うちどうしたの？何かこう、お菓子がいっぱいあるっていうから…
Eh, what happened? They said there were tons of sweets here...
え、だからパーティーの招待状来たけど、そんなの送った覚え…
Eh, we got party invitations, but I don't remember sending any...
え、でも私やっぱケーキも食いたいー！ケーキ食べたいと思ってたんだよねー！
Eh, but I still want to eat cake! I was thinking I wanted to eat cake!
いや、でもさ、これ、え？本当にここで食べるの？
Wait, but, is this... are we really eating here?
なんかちょっと硬い。なんか、おい！おい！これ…
It's kind of hard. Like, hey! Hey! This...
えー、夢の味？何何何？
Eh, the taste of a dream? What, what, what?
え、何何、二人ともね、本当は、何々、何しに来てくれたの？
Eh, what, you two, really, what did you come here to do?
え、もうただ、え、食べに来たって聞いたけどさ、え、でも、ねえ！ねえ！ねえ！あげてか、ねえ、言って、言って、言って！
We just heard you came to eat, but hey! Say it!
じゃあ行くよ。せーの！
Then here we go. Ready, set!
ルーナ、2周年おめでとうー！
Luna, happy 2nd anniversary!
え、2歳になったか？2歳？2歳？
Eh, did you turn 2 years old? 2 years old?
いや、2歳じゃねえんだけどな！で、僕たちが出会って、2歳の誕生日なんだね！
No, you're not turning 2! But it's the 2nd anniversary since we met!
今日誕生日じゃねえから！2周年だから！そう、間違えないでほしいんだよ！
It's not my birthday! It's the 2nd anniversary! Don't get it wrong!
いや、でもさ、もうお立ち、お立ちができる！え、もうできてる！
Yeah, but you can stand up now! Eh, you can already do it!
みんなも随分大きくなっちまってよー！
Everyone's grown up so much!
ま、姫だからな、わしは姫ぞ！
Well, I'm a princess, I'm a princess!
え、でも、せっかくだからさ、この3人で、あんぽんたんシスターズで一緒にね…
Eh, but since we're here, the three of us, the Anpontan Sisters...
あの、歌って踊ってほしいのになの！
Um, we want you to sing and dance, nano!
それはおねだり上手ね？
You're good at begging, aren't you?
あら、おねだり……踊ってくれる？
Oh, begging... Will you dance for us?
今日はルナの言うこと全部聞いてあげる！
Today, I'll listen to everything Luna says!
わあ！
Yay!
うれしい、え、どうしようかな？
I'm so happy... Um, what should I do?
なんだよ、どうしようじゃねえよ、お前たち
Hey now, don't give me that "what should I do" stuff!
おとなしくして、今日は
Be good today.
すごーい！楽しみ！
Amazing! I'm so excited!
じゃあ、3人で一緒に歌おうのだ！
Then let the three of us sing together!
歌おうのだ！
Let's sing!
揺り揺り揺れている 乙女心ピ~ンチ!
Swinging, swaying, maiden's heart in a pinch!
かなりかなりヤバいのよ
It's really, really dangerous!
たすけてダーリン!クラクラリン
Help me, darling! Spinning around!
何もかもが新しい世界にきちゃったわ
Everything got tangled in a brand new world!
たくさんのドキドキ 乗りこえ! 踏みこえ! イクぞ!
Overcoming many heart-pounding moments! Let's go!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
この想いは止められない!
I can't stop this feeling!
もっと乙女ちっくパワー きらりんにん
More maiden-chic power, sparkling bright!
ちょっと危険なカンジ
A bit of a risky vibe!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
もうドキドキ止められない もっとドラマチック恋ハレルヤ
I can't stop my pounding heart, more dramatic love hallelujah!
二人だけの バラライカ!
Our very own balalaika!
すごくすごく近づいて 乙女心チャ~ンス!
Getting closer and closer, maiden's heart chance!
ハートハート飛び出そう おねがいダーリン!
Heart, heart about to leap, please darling!
あなただけを見つめてるワタシにしらんぷり?
Feigning ignorance of me who's only looking at you?
気づいてほしいのよ トキメキ! ヤキモチ! スキよ!
I want you to notice, excitement, jealousy, I love you!
その秘密を教えてよ もっと乙女ちっくモード
Tell me that secret, more maiden-chic mode!
やっぱ笑顔がステキ よそみしちゃダメダメよ
Smiling is best, don't you dare look away!
もっと乙女ちっく恋シャラランラン
More maiden-chic love shararanran!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
その秘密を教えてよ もっと乙女ちっくモード
Tell me that secret, more maiden-chic mode!
もっとドラマチック恋ハレルヤ 二人だけの バラライカ!
More dramatic love hallelujah, our very own balalaika!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
ときめきの中なでたいの バラライカ
I want to stroke within the excitement, balalaika!
女の子はいつでも夢見る乙女なの
Girls are always dreaming maidens!
ぴゅあぴゅあな心に 恋して愛して S・O・S!
In a pure, pure heart, fall in love, love S.O.S!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
この想いは止められない!
I can't stop this feeling!
もっと乙女ちっくパワー きらりんにん
More maiden-chic power, sparkling bright!
ちょっと危険なカンジ
A bit of a risky vibe!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
もうドキドキ止められない もっとドラマチック恋ハレルヤ
I can't stop my pounding heart, more dramatic love hallelujah!
二人だけの バラライカ!
Our very own balalaika!
バラライカ バラライカ バラ ライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, bala lailai kaikai!
ときめきの中なでたいの バラライカ
I want to stroke within the excitement, balalaika!
女の子はいつでも夢見る乙女なの
Girls are always dreaming maidens!
ぴゅあぴゅあな心に 恋して愛して S・O・S!
In a pure, pure heart, fall in love, love S.O.S!
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカ...
Balalaika, balalaika, balalaika...
1! 2! 3! 4!
I want you! I need you! I love you!
頭の中ガンガン鳴ってるMUSIC ヘビーローテーション
Inside my head, music keeps playing, heavy rotation!
ポップコーンが弾けるように 好きという文字が踊る
Like popcorn popping, the words "I love you" are dancing!
顔や声を想うだけで 居ても立ってもいられない
Just by thinking of your face or voice, I can't sit still!
こんな気持ちになれるって 僕はついているね
To be able to feel like this, I am so lucky!
I want you! I need you! I love you! 君に会えてどんどん近づくその距離にMAX ハイテンション
I want you! I need you! I love you! Since I met you, the distance between us is getting shorter and shorter, putting me in a max high-tension mood!
1, 2, 3, 4!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
頭の中 ガンガン鳴ってるMUSIC
Inside my head, music keeps playing,
ヘビーローテーション
Heavy rotation!
ポップコーンが 弾けるように
Like popcorn popping,
好き という 文字が踊る
The words "I love you" are dancing.
顔や声を 想うだけで
Just by thinking of your face or voice,
居ても立っても いられない
I just can't sit still.
こんな気持ちに なれるって
To be able to feel like this,
僕はついているね
I am so lucky!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
君に会えて ドンドン近づく
Since I met you, we get closer and closer,
その距離に MAX ハイテンション
And this distance puts me in MAX high tension!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
ハートの奥 ジャンジャン溢れる
Inside my heart, my affection overflows endlessly,
愛しさは ヘビーローテーション
My love is a heavy rotation!
人は誰も 一生のうちは
How many times can anyone fall in love
何回愛せるのだろう?
In the span of a lifetime?
たった一度 忘れられない 恋ができたら満足さ
If I could have just one unforgettable love, I'd be satisfied.
そんなときめきを感じて 花は綻ぶのかな
Maybe flowers start to bloom when they feel such excitement.
I feel you!
I touch you!
I hold you!
夢の中で ダンダン大きくなって行く 僕のイマジネーション
Inside my dreams, my imagination grows bigger and bigger.
I feel you!
I touch you!
I hold you!
この想いを ビンビン伝えて欲しいから ヘビーローテーション
Because I want you to feel this strong emotion, heavy rotation!
いつも聴いてた favorite song
My favorite song that I always listened to,
あの曲のようにずっと繰り返して
Just like that song, repeating endlessly,
24時間 君だけリクエスト中
24 hours a day, requesting only you!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
君に会えて ドンドン近づく
Since I met you, we get closer and closer,
その距離に MAX ハイテンション
And this distance puts me in MAX high tension!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
ハートの奥 ジャンジャン溢れる
Inside my heart, my affection overflows endlessly,
愛しさは ヘビーローテーション
My love is a heavy rotation!
いつも聞いてた Favorite song あの曲のようにずっと繰り返して
Always listening to my favorite song, repeating it like that track,
24時間 君だけリクエスト中
24 hours a day, requesting only you!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
君に会えて ドンドン近づく その距離に MAX ハイテンション
Since I met you, the distance gets closer and closer, putting me in MAX high tension!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
ハートの奥 ジャンジャン溢れる 愛しさは ヘビーローテーション
Inside my heart, my affection overflows endlessly, love is a heavy rotation!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
君に会えて ドンドン近づく その距離に MAX ハイテンション
Since I met you, we get closer and closer, and this distance puts me in MAX high tension!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
ハートの奥 ジャンジャン溢れる 愛しさは ヘビーローテーション
Inside my heart, my affection overflows endlessly, love is a heavy rotation!
ヘビーローテーション
Heavy rotation!
うー
Ugh...
え、ちょっと大丈夫なの？
Eh, wait, are you okay?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
踊っただけ疲れてるけど...
I'm just tired from dancing, though...
大丈夫？ お水、お水どこ？
Are you okay? Water, where's the water?
お水飲んだあと...
After drinking water...
お水飲もう。二人とも元気なのらね。
Let's drink some water. You two are so energetic, nora.
まだまだ、まだまだ！
Not yet, not yet!
まだまだ全然、全然行けちゃうのら？
We can still totally keep going, nora?
え、ちょっと、ちょっと...
Eh, wait, wait...
その、いけるステップとかできちゃうってなのはら？
That you can still do those steps and stuff, nora?
しょうがないの、ロボ子な感じとか？
It can't be helped, like Roboco's vibe?
え、お水でくんのら？
Eh, you're gonna go get water, nora?
え、やばい、やばい、ロボ子すぎる！
Eh, no way, no way, that's so Roboco!
え、そんな踊れすぎるのなにそれ？
Eh, how can you dance that much? What is that?
ロボ子、このステップとかできるの？え、どこ？ロボ子もできるけど...
Roboco, can you do this step? Eh, where? Roboco can do it too, but...
え、ちょっとやってみるの？
Eh, wanna try doing it a bit?
もう一回、お水出る？もう一回お水出る？行くよ！
Let's get water again? Let's get water again? Here we go!
なんかズレてない？ なんかズレてない？ ロボットじゃズレてない！
Are we out of sync? Are we out of sync? Robots wouldn't be out of sync!
踊ってないステップ無理だよー！
Dancing steps without music is impossible!
でもなんかこのアンポンタンシスターズで踊るのめっちゃ久しぶりじゃねーの？
Isn't it been ages since we danced as these stupid sisters?
そうだねー！ルーナさ、なんでこの2曲選択したの？
That's right! Luna, why did you choose these two songs?
え？まずね、この「バラライカ」！どうしてかっていうと、アキロゼ先輩を最初イメージして…
Eh? First, this 'Baralika'! Why? Because I initially pictured Aki Rosenthal-senpai...
え？それってもしや…
Eh? Could that be...
UFOかなって！UFOって言ってる！なんかこれイメージしたらアキロゼ先輩…
UFO! She's saying UFO! When I pictured that, Aki Rosenthal-senpai...
むっきゅんて！拳のほや、それは…！むきむきの筋肉！
Mukyun! A fist... that's muscular muscles!
なんかぴったりなんだよねえと思ったから、この曲…
I thought it fit so well, so this song...
え、何じまったんだよー？
Wait, what's going on?
いやなんか楽しすぎた！あ、愛のって言って貰えればよかった！
Man, it was too fun! Ah, I wish you had said 'love'!
UFOって言って貰えればよかったのに！え、伸びて？
I wish you had said UFO! Eh, stretched?
でもね、「バラライカ」！でもちょっとこれを歌ったらやっぱ最後はさ、アイドルっぽい曲歌いたいなと、可愛さ欲求したいのね。
But 'Baralika'! If we sing 'Baralika', at the end we want to sing an idol-like song and satisfy our cuteness desire.
それで「コネビル」でしょ？3人で踊れたらやっぱ…
That's why 'Connect'? If the three of us could dance, then...
最高だったね！3人で踊れたのめっちゃ嬉しかった！
It was the best! I was so happy we could dance together!
前にさ、はるみんとさ、歌歌った時さ、もうなんかグダグダだったじゃん！
Before, when you and Harumin sang together, it was all messy!
今回成長したね！成長したんだよ！3人ともめっちゃ成長したんだよ！成長したって感じがするよ！
We grew this time! We really grew! All three of us grew so much! I feel like we've grown.
うれしー！ありがとう！2人ともほんと今日ありがとうね、来てくれて！おめでとう！
I'm so happy! Thank you! Thank you both so much for coming today! Congratulations!
ありがとう！この後も楽しんでね！おめでとー！がんばるね！がんばるね！ありがとう！
Thank you! Enjoy the rest of the show! Congratulations! I'll do my best! Thank you!
おっしゃ！バイバーイ！またね！バイバーイ！行くんだよー！水たまり！みんな、ありがとう！
Alright! Bye-bye! See you! Bye-bye! We're going! Puddle! Everyone, thank you!
はぁー、楽しかった！でももっともっとみんなと歌いたいのよね。
Hah, that was fun! But I want to sing with everyone even more.
おーの！スパチョコに会いにいくなら…！
Oh no! If we're going to meet Choco-sen...
おい、あすま、早口違うの！
Hey, Asuma, fast talking is different!
間に合わないわよ！間に合わないわよ！しょうがないでしょ、ちょっと話が…
We won't make it in time! We won't make it in time! It can't be helped, the talk is...
ちょっとちょっと待ってだから！ちょっと待って！ルーナも混ぜて！
Wait, wait a minute! Wait! Include Luna too!
いや、混ぜらねぇよ！混ぜません！入れてよ！
No, we can't include you! We won't! Let me in!
いや入れませんけど、ちょっとあの場所がここでややこしいんで、場所展開します！
We won't let you in, but since the location here is complicated, we'll change locations!
いやややこしい！場所展開します！ほら、るなちゃん。
It's complicated! We'll change locations! Look, Luna-chan.
えっ、どうしたの？えっ、今日、えっ、今日実はね、るなの2周年記念でね、ライブしてたんだよー！
Eh, what happened? Eh, today, eh, actually today, Luna was having her 2nd anniversary live!
あ、そうなの？おめでとう！
Oh really? Congratulations!
あ、ありがとうね！ちょっと待って！ちょっと待って！お前ふざけんなね！
Ah, thank you! Wait! Wait a minute! Don't mess around!
え、どうしたのどうしたの？えっ、何でるながわざわざここにきたのはね、せっかくだからスパチョコルーナでね、手をつなぎ合って踊り手踊りって…
Eh, what happened? Why did you come here all the way? Since it's a rare chance, Supa-Choco-Luna holding hands and dancing...
なるほどね、しょうがないわね、もう！歌ってくれる？踊ってくれる？じゃあね…
I see, it can't be helped, jeez! Will you sing? Will you dance? Well then...
まぁしょうがねぇな！せっかくだからね！じゃあ歌おう！いくぞー！
Well, it can't be helped! Since it's a special occasion! Let's sing! Here we go!
我々！(うー！)寄り依れ！(にゃー！)
We! (Woo!) Gather around! (Nya!)
世界はDark！(こずみっく！)
The world is Dark! (Cosmic!)
心ねるねる異形の神々 私もあなたも畏れの物笑い
Restless, formless strange gods, you and I are both objects of dread and mockery.
形むるむる異教徒逃げれば 私とあなたはお天道様でおデート
Shapeless heretics fleeing, you and I are on a date under the blazing sun.
た の し い ね 焼けるぜ溶けるぜ (生き物じゃなーい)
It's so fun, burning and melting (not a living creature)
骨 ひやひや其れでも好きです
Bones chilling, but I still love it
私がいちばん欲しいのは内緒よ
What I want most of all is a secret
姿ぱりぱり其れでは行きましょう
Crispy appearance, let's go with that
私にいちばん似合うかな不条理
What suits me best? Absurdity
鏡には (だん だん 誰なのは？)
In the mirror (Dan dan, who is it?)
うつらない (誰なんだ？やだやだ)
Doesn't reflect (Who is it? No, no!)
欲望は言葉にしなくちゃいちゃ (うー！)
Desires must be put into words (Woo!)
ほら (にゃー！)、消えちゃうんでしょう？ (レッツにゃー！)
Look (Nya!), it'll disappear, won't it? (Let's Nya!)
太陽なんか眩しくって
The sun is too dazzling,
吾々! (うー!)
Wawa! (Woo!)
寄り依り! (にゃー!)
Yori yori! (Nya!)
世界はDark! (こずみっく!)
Sekai wa Dark! (Cosmic!)
心ぬるぬる異形の神々
Slimy, slippery, grotesque deities,
私もあなたも恐れの物ずき
Both you and I are morbidly curious.
形むろむろ異教徒逃げれば
Shifting, squirming heretics, if you run away,
私とあなたはおデート
You and I will have a date under the sun.
たのしいね
Isn't it fun?
焼けるぞ溶けるぞ (生き物じゃなーい)
It's burning, melting (Not a living creature!)
骨ひらひら其れでも好きです
Bones fluttering, but I still love it.
私がいちばん欲しいのは内緒よ
What I want most of all is a secret.
姿ちらちら其れでは行きましょう
Silhouettes flickering, let's go then.
私にいちばん似合うかな不条理
Does it suit me best? Such absurdity.
鏡には (だんだん誰なのは?)
In the mirror (Gradually, who is it?)
うつらない (誰なんだ?やだよやだよ)
Doesn't reflect (Who is it? No, no!)
欲望は言葉にしなくちゃ (うー!)
Desires must be put into words (Woo!)
ほら (にゃー!) 消え失せちゃうでしょう?
Look (Nya!), it'll vanish into thin air,
(レッツにゃー!)
won't it? (Let's Nya!)
うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー!
Woo! Nya! Woo! Nya!
太陽なんか眩しくって 闇のほうが素敵よ (にゃー!)
The sun is too dazzling, darkness is lovelier (Nya!)
太陽ばっか眩しくって 闇のほうがす・て・き (にゃんご~?)
The sun is just too blinding, darkness is lo... lovely (Meow~?)
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS
燃えよ混沌 無敵です (わくわく)
Burn, chaos, you're invincible (So excited)
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS
燃えるようなき・も・ち (にゃんげ~?)
A burning sensation (Meow-ge~?)
吾々! (うー!) 遣り破れ! (にゃー!)
Wawa! (Woo!) Yari yabure! (Nya!)
世界はDark! (こずみっく!)
Sekai wa Dark! (Cosmic!)
枕ぽかぽか無貌の神々
Pillows fluffy, faceless deities,
私とあなたと目的は違うの
You and I have different purposes.
絆むかむか無理矢理されがち
Bonds nauseating, often forced upon me.
私があなたを守るけどおピンチ
I'll protect you, but it's a tight spot.
お か し い な
How strange.
逃げるぞ悴むぞ (狙われてるーぅ)
Running away, hands freezing (Being targeted—)
帳おりおり此処まで来ました
Curtains falling, we've come this far.
私はだまって敵たちを蹂躙する
I silently trample the enemies.
燃えらめらめら此処では駄目です
Blazing, flickering, this place is no good.
私にだまってスカウトはしないで
Don't scout behind my back.
望むなら (ぜん ぜん 全滅!)
If you wish (Total annihilation!)
しましょうね (敵なんだ?やれやれ)
Let's do it (An enemy? Good grief)
願わくば跡形もなくね (うー!)
I pray without a trace left (Woo!)
あら (にゃー!) 要らないでしょう? (レッツにゃー!)
Oh (Nya!), you don't need it? (Let's Nya!)
現在なんと危険だった
How dangerous it was right now.
光りもんを下され (ぴかぴか)
Give me some shiny things (Sparkle, sparkle)
現在なんとぞ危険だった
It was really dangerous right now.
ひとりもんでしげき (やらし~)
Being single is a stimulus (Indecent~)
MADNESS MADNESS you wanna madness
避けれるほどに過激です (ぞくぞく)
Too radical to avoid (Thrilling)
MADNESS MADNESS ennui madness
避ければきっとおしまい (なんです!)
If you avoid it, it's the end (That's right!)
マネス・マンネス アニュイ・マンネス
Maness, Maness, Ennui Maness,
呼べばきっとおしまい
If you call, it's definitely the end.
はいよ (うー!) ここ (にゃー!)
Haiyo (Woo!) Koko (Nya!)
やるならとことん
If you're gonna do it, go all the way.
うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー!
Woo! Nya! Woo! Nya!
れッツにゃー!
Let's go!
太陽なんか眩しくって
The sun is so dazzling,
闇のほうが無限で どきどき
the darkness is infinite, thumping.
太陽ばっか眩しくって
The sun is just too dazzling,
闇のほうがすてき (にゃんご~?)
the darkness is lovely (Meow-go~?)
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS
燃えよ混沌 無敵です (わくわく)
Burn, chaos, you're invincible (So excited)
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS
燃えるようなきもち (にゃんげ~?)
A burning feeling (Meow-nge~?)
マンネス・マンネス アニュイ・マンネス
Maness, Maness, Annyui Maness,
呼べばきっとおしまい
If you call, it's definitely the end.
はいよ (うー!) ここ (にゃー!) やるならとことん!
Haiyo (Woo!) Koko (Nya!) Yaru nara tocoton!
踊ったー! みんな大丈夫?
We danced! Is everyone okay?
全然! 全然元気だね!
Totally fine! We're full of energy!
三人で踊れたね! イエーイ! イエーイ!
We were able to dance together as three! Yay!
なんかこないだも踊った気がするけどね!
I feel like we did this recently too!
ルナちゃんおめでとう!
Luna-chan, congratulations!
ありがとう! ありがとうね! また三人で踊れてね!
Thank you! Thank you! We danced together again!
うれしいうれしい、ありがとうね!
Luna is so happy! Thank you!
満足した? まだ満足してない!
Are you satisfied? I'm not satisfied yet!
まだあるの? よくばりさんなんだから!
There's still more?! Because we're greedy!
次次はね、いまね、すばちょこるな って踊ったからさ
Next is... right now we danced "Subachoc Luna"...
おっ! とっ!? すばちょこるなたんってね!
Oh! What? "Subachoc Luna Tun"?!
歌って踊りてぇのとな!
So we want to sing and dance!
いいね! いっぱい踊ろうね! おっしゃ!
That's great! Let's dance more!
いくぞ、いくぞ、いくぞ!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
ボタンちゃん!
Botan-chan!
お疲れ様! みんな! お疲れ様!
Good work, everyone! Good work!
お待たせよ! きたよ!
Kept you waiting! We're here!
え、今日何々? 何するの?
Eh, what's today? What are we doing?
え、今日、実はね、ルナ2周年記念ライブしてるのよ!
Actually, Luna's 2nd anniversary live is today!
おめでとー!
Congratulations!
ひとりづつ仲間集めてんだ今!
We're gathering friends one by one right now!
まじ!?
Seriously!?
そう、今メンバー揃ったのよ!
Yeah, all the members are gathered now!
おぉ!
Oh!
あ、もうボス倒しに行く感じ?
Ah, are we going to defeat the boss now?
行く! 行く行く! 一緒に倒しに行くぞ!
Let's go! Let's go defeat it together!
行くぞ! 行くぞ!
Let's go! Let's go!
じゃあみんな フォーメーション展開なのだ!
Then everyone, formation deployment!
なに? フォーメーション!?
What? Formation!?
みんな並んでフォーメーション! 集中集中集中!
Everyone line up in formation! Focus!
シャキーン! じゃきーん! じゃきん!
Shakin'! Jakin'! Shakin'!
いくわよ! どきゅーん! じょいふる!
Here we go! Dokyun! Joyful!
キミノコエヲキカセテ
Let me hear your voice,
サアボウケンシテミナイ
come on, why don’t we have an adventure?
タノシイコトハジメヨウ
Let's start something fun,
遊びたい、絶対、絶対、たい！
I really wanna play!
あいわな JOYと JOYと JOYと ポプなベイベー
I wanna... Joy and joy and joy and poppy baby,
JOYと JOYと JOYと ハピなピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people!
よゆうしなんかない
I have no time to spare,
じしんありげなピースサイン
flashing a confident peace sign.
キミノヒトミにキスして
I want to kiss your eyes,
笑いたい、絶対、絶対、たい！
and I really, really want to smile!
あいわな JOYと JOYと JOYと ポプなベイベー
I wanna... Joy and joy and joy and poppy baby,
JOYと JOYと JOYと ハピなセイエーイ
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
キミノココロはそうもっと Doo Doo
Your heart does, does more,
ボクのココロもそういっそ Good Good
and my heart feels more good, good.
はじけてるんじゃない? イッツ じょいふる
Aren't we bursting out? It's joyful!
ぱぴぷぺぽ ばぶー いぇい！
Papipupepo babuu, yay!
JOYと JOYと JOYと ポプなベイベー
Joy and joy and joy and poppy baby,
JOYと JOYと JOYと ハピなセイエーイ
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
ドキドキちゃうのなんでだろ
Why am I getting so nervous?
ズキズキちゃうのなんでだろ
Why does my heart throb like this?
この指にとまるのはどんな運命なんだ全部たいな
What fate lies on this finger? I want it all!
じょいふるだって終わっちゃう エビバデイいつか終わっちゃう
Even joyful times end, everybody's time ends someday.
いついつまでもこの時の最終形はきっと修正なしで
Forever and ever, the final form of this moment needs no fixes.
We do We do We do...
ぱぴぷぺぽ ぱぴぷぺ ぱぴぷぺ ばぶー いぇい！
Pipupepo pipupe pipupe babuu, yay!
JOYと JOYと JOYと ポプなベイベー
Joy and joy and joy and poppy baby,
JOYと JOYと JOYと ハピなセイエーイ
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
キミノココロはそうもっと Doo Doo
Your heart does, does more,
ボクのココロもそういっそ Good Good
and my heart feels more good, good.
はじけてるんじゃない? イッツ じょいふる
Aren't we bursting out? It's joyful!
ぱぴぷぺぽ ぱぴぷぺ ぱぴぷぺ ばぶー
Papipupepo pipupe pipupe babuu,
JOY
せーの スノーハレーション！
Ready, set, Snow halation!
不思議だね いまの気持ち
It's strange, this current feeling,
空から降ってきたみたい
like it came falling from the sky.
特別な季節の色が とめきを見せるよ
The special colors of this season show excitement.
初めて出会った時から
Ever since the first time we met,
予感に騒ぐ心のMelody
the melody of our hearts stirs with premonition.
とまれない とまらない な・ぜ
Unstoppable, won't stop, tell me why.
届けて 切なさには名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
Reach out—let's give this pain a name: "Snow halation."
想いが重なるまで待てずに
Without waiting for our feelings to align,
悔しいけれど好きって純情
it's frustrating, but this pure love of "I love you"
微熱の中ためらってもだめだね
won't hold back even amidst a slight fever.
飛び込む勇気に賛成 まもなくStart!!
Approve the courage to jump in—start is soon!
音もなく 気配もなく
Without a sound, without a trace,
静かに運命は変わる
fate quietly changes.
これからの未来に胸の
For the future ahead,
鼓動が早くなる
our heartbeats quicken.
例えば困ったときには
For example, when in trouble,
すぐ駆けつけて抱きしめたくて
I want to rush over and hold you tight.
どこにいてもどこでも Fly high
No matter where you are, fly high!
急いで いつの間にか
Hastily, before we knew it,
大きくなりすぎた True emotion
our true emotions grew too large.
夢だけでもってるんじゃないよ
It's not just about dreaming,
恋人は君って言いたい
I want to say "You're my lover."
優しい目がとまどってるイヤだよ
I hate seeing your gentle eyes confused.
このまま一気に愛情あずけてPlease!!
Entrust all your love to me right now, please!
届けて 切なさには名前をつけようか
Convey it! Let's give this pain a name:
スノーハレーション
Snow halation!
想いが重なるまで待てずに
Without waiting for our feelings to overlap,
悔しいけど好きって純情
it's frustrating, but this pure love is "I love you."
微熱の中ためらってもだめだね
Even if I hesitate in this slight fever, it's no good.
飛び込む勇気に賛成まもなくStart!!
Approve the courage to jump in—Start soon!
よかったー！
That was great!
That was wonderful!
おめでとうー！おめでとうー！
Congratulations! Congratulations!
ありがとうなのー！
Thank you so much!
すば！今日も来てくれて！
Everyone came today!
歌唱ちゃん、今日は来てくれてありがとうー！
Thank you so much for coming today!
こちらこそ、ありがとうー！おめでとうー！
Thank you too! Congratulations!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
じゃあルーナ、最後までがんばってな！
Luna, do your best until the end!
頑張るの！頑張るの！
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
がんばれー！おめでとうー！またねー！
Good luck! Congratulations! See you later!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
ルーナが今、二周年を迎えられたのは、ルーナとホロライブのみんなのおかげなのだ！
The reason Luna could reach her 2nd anniversary is thanks to Luna and everyone in Hololive!
次はこの歌を歌います！
Next, I will sing this song!
好きになって！ もっと！ 私を見て！ もっと！
Fall in love with me more! Look at me more!
恩返しは “愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is with a "love-filled flying kiss"!
気のせいじゃない 目は合ってるよ
It's not my imagination, our eyes are meeting!
ハート作って 恋しちゃってください！
Make a heart and fall in love with me!
やれること 何でも します
I'll do whatever it takes,
NGなしで 体当たり 挑戦
taking on any challenge head-on with no restrictions!
エゴサで見つけた アンチのコメント
The anti comments I found from ego-searching—
ふざけンな…！ 誰より分かってるし
Cut the crap...! I know that better than anyone,
でも大丈夫 ステージに立てばみんながいる
but it's okay, when I stand on stage, everyone is here.
好きになって！ もっと！ 私を見て！ もっと！
Fall in love with me more! Look at me more!
恩返しは “愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is with a "love-filled flying kiss"!
眩くする！ もっと！ 夢を見せる！ もっと！
Dazzle me more! Show me dreams more!
楽しんできいて 愛のこもった スペシャルナイト
Enjoy and listen to this love-filled special night!
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me! More! Look at me! More!
恩返しは “愛のこもった投げキスで”
My repayment is a love-filled flying kiss!
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you fan service!
♡作って 恋しちゃってください！
Make a heart... and fall in love with me!
やれること 何でもします
I'll do whatever it takes,
NGなしで 体当たり挑戦
taking on any challenge head-on with no restrictions!
エゴサで見つけた アンチのコメ
Finding anti comments when searching myself...
ぶざけんな…！
Are you kidding me...?!
誰より分かってるし でも大丈夫
I understand better than anyone, but it's okay,
ステージに立てばみんながいる （行くよ！）
when I stand on stage, everyone is here! (Here we go!)
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me! More! Look at me! More!
恩返しは “愛のこもった投げキスで”
My repayment is a love-filled flying kiss!
虜にする！もっと！夢を見せる！もっと！
I'll captivate you! More! Show you dreams! More!
楽しんできて 愛のこもった スペシャルナイト
Enjoy it all in this love-filled special night,
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you fan service!
お手紙も書いてください！
Please write me letters too!
何度も読んで 宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and treasure them.
スキャンダルまだ早いけど
A scandal is still too early, but
裏切りません！ 宣言しときます
I won't betray you! I declare that right now.
嫉妬、嫌がらせには 負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment!
ぶざけんな！ 実力で勝ってやる
Are you kidding me?! I'll win with pure skill!
だからやめない 負けず嫌い 私はいる （行くよ！）
That's why I won't stop; I'm a sore loser, and I'm right here! (Here we go!)
こぶし上げて！もっと！汗をかいて！もっと！
Raise your fists! More! Work up a sweat! More!
恩返しは “愛のこもったmonaビームで”
My repayment is with a love-filled Mona beam!
大歓声！もっと！まだまだ！？ねぇ！もっと！
Loud cheers! More! Still not enough?! Hey! More!
受け止めてね 愛のこもった わがままソング
Please accept my love-filled selfish song,
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you fan service!
はぁ… 終わりが近づく 寂しいね
Hah... The end is drawing near, it's so lonely.
楽しいのに 泣きそうだよ
Even though it's fun, I feel like crying.
次も 次も また会えるよね？ （約束！）
We'll meet again and again, right? (Promise!)
優しさにあふれている 言葉も 心ない誰かのとか 言葉さえも
Words overflowing with kindness, and even the heartless words of someone else—
必要なんだ 強く なろう
they're all necessary. Let's become strong.
好きに叫べ！もっと！楽しんじゃお！もっと！
Shout out whatever you like! More! Have fun! More!
忘れないで 特別な日 になりますように
Don't forget, so that this can become a special day.
共に歌おう ずっと！ 共に歩もう ずっと！
Let's sing together forever! Let's walk together forever!
合言葉は とびっきりの I・O・V・E
The password is an amazing I-O-V-E!
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me! More! Look at me! More!
恩返しは “愛のこもった投げキスで”
My repayment is a love-filled flying kiss!
と お祝いしてくれて
...for celebrating with me.
みんなのファンサどうだったのかな？
How was everyone's fan service?
うん、コメント見る。
Yeah, let me check the comments.
みんなみんな泣いてるのか？
Is everyone crying?
るるらは泣いてねえぞ、るるらは泣いてねえぞ、こんな。
Rurura isn't crying! Rurura isn't crying, like this.
みんなすぐ泣くんだから、すぐ泣く、泣いたらすぐ泣いた。
Everyone cries right away, if you cry, you cry instantly.
るるらは泣いてねえからな。
Rurura isn't crying, you know!
みんな、よかった？ほんと？泣いてる、泣いてる気持ちは、最高だった、ほんと。
Everyone, was it good? Really? You're crying, your feelings of crying, it was the best, really.
ありがとう、みんな聞いてくれて。
Thank you everyone for listening.
胸がいっぱいなのだよ。
My heart is so full.
でもちょっとみんな、ここからは2周年記念で、うちの方紹介していきいと思うのだよ。みんな落ち着いて。
But hey everyone, from here on, for the 2nd anniversary, I'd like to introduce our goods. Everyone calm down.
見て！みんなみんな、可愛いでしょ？
Look! Everyone, aren't they cute?
姫森るな2周年記念グッズは、こちら全部で4種類あります。早速見ていくのだよ！
There are 4 types of Himemori Luna 2nd anniversary merchandise in total. Let's take a look right away!
じゃあ、まずはかんざきパパ描き下ろしのラバーマットです。
So, first is the rubber mat illustrated by Kanzaki Papa.
ドレス姿のルナと新衣装のワンピースのルナがね、ついにになったかわいいイラストなのだよ！
Luna in a dress and Luna in her new one-piece outfit finally together, what a cute illustration!
10月にルナ誕生日記念グッズとして出したおぺま...
Released in October as Luna's birthday commemorative goods, opema...
パッとあるの、でしょ？
You have that right away, right?
あれに合わせて、
Matching that,
ディスク周りをね、
to enrich your desk setup,
充実させようと、
I made it into
ラバーマットにしたのなよ！
a rubber mat!
そして次こちら！
And next, this one!
先生かきおろしのBIGなメガネ置きアクリルスタンド！
A big glasses-resting acrylic stand newly drawn by Kanzaki-sensei!
こちらはね、なんと約40cmもあるね、大きいサイズのメガネ置きアクリルスタンドなのだよ！
This one is about 40cm tall—a large-sized glasses-resting acrylic stand!
メガネでもサングラスでもね、どのサングラスするかね、好きなものをルナにねここにつけてほしいなら！
Whether it's glasses or sunglasses, I'd love for you to attach your favorite to Luna right here!
そして次！
And next!
パッパね、かきおろしラバーマットと同じイラストで、クリーナークロスもあるのだよ！
With the same illustration as the newly drawn rubber mat, there's also a cleaner cross!
さっきのね、BIGメガネ置きアクリルスタンド、メガネってね、こちらお大きめのサイズになってるから、メガネ拭きにも使えるし、
Since the big glasses-resting acrylic stand from earlier is quite large, you can use it to wipe glasses,
パソコンとか、あのパッドとか、マルチにも使える、一品になっているのだよ！
and it's a versatile item you can use on PCs or tablets!
そして次！
And next!
ルーナイト紋章ピンバッチー！
The Lunaknight Crest Pin Badge!
ルナのモチーフがふんだんに盛り込まれた、素敵なデザインになっているのだよ！
It has a wonderful design filled to the brim with Luna's motifs!
こちらもね、10月の誕生日記念グッズとして出したマグカップと同じデザインになってるのだよ！かわいい！
This also has the same design as the mug released for October's birthday commemoration! Cute!
ピンバッチはね、このピンクのね、かわいい箱に入れて、みんなに、お届けします！
The pin badge will be delivered to everyone in this cute pink box!
そしてそして！こちらフルセットご購入の方限定のポストカードとボイスの特典があります！
And then, and then! For those who purchase the full set, there are exclusive postcard and voice bonuses!
フルセット限定で直筆サインとメッセージ入りのポストカード＋特典ボイスがついてくるのだよ！
The full-set exclusive comes with a postcard featuring a handwritten autograph and message, plus bonus voice tracks!
特典ボイスにはね、ルナの今までの生ー夢とか、いろんなお話をね、収録してあるので、ぜひ、聞いてほしいな！
The bonus voice tracks include Luna's past dreams and various stories recorded, so I definitely want you to listen to them!
そして、最後！重大発表なのだよ！
And finally! A major announcement!
長らくお待たせしてしまった、
I've kept you waiting for a long time,
ルナのオリジナルソングをお披露目します！
I'll be unveiling Luna's original song!
みんなね、いっぱいいっぱい待たせてしまって、ごめんなならね！
Everyone, I'm so sorry for making you wait so much!
こちらね、1月中にはダウンロード配信できる予定で、ジャケットのイラストはね、かげきパパに描いてもらっているのです！
This is scheduled for digital release in January, and the jacket illustration was drawn by Kageki-papa!
またわかり次第、みんなに告知するならね！楽しみに待ってほしいなら！
I'll announce it to everyone as soon as I know more! I hope you're looking forward to it!
姫森ルナ活動2周年記念ルーナイトたち、これからもルナのそばにいてください！
Himemori Luna 2nd Anniversary, Lunaknights, please continue to stay by Luna's side!
それでは歌います！しーぱっともあるので、最後までぜひぜひ見てください！
Now I'll sing! There's also a 3D part, so please be sure to watch until the very end!
絶対忠誠なのだなー！
Absolute loyalty, nanonana!
んなああああ
Nnaaaaaa
みんなおりゅ～？(° o °)
Everyone, where are you~? (° o °)
なのなのら！
Nanonanora!
絶対忠誠♡なのなのら！
Absolute loyalty ♡ nanonanora!
お菓子の国のお姫様 とびきりプリティーな0歳児
Princess of the candy land, a super pretty 0-year-old
ピアノだって弾けるんだし 赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I can even play the piano, you know, I'm not a baby!
ワガママだって言うけれど ルナはお姫様なのだから
You might call me selfish, but Luna is a princess after all
ルーナイト達も執事も いちいちうるさいのら！
Lunaknights and butlers alike, you're all so noisy!
さぁルーナイト達 準備はできたのら〜？
Now, Lunaknights, are you ready~?
出陣なのら〜！
Marching out, nanora~!
出陣なのら～！
Let's deploy, nanora~!
パフェもしゅわしゅわも
Parfaits and fizzy drinks,
早く用意するのら！
get them ready quickly, nanora!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that too!
おいしいのはひとりじめ♪
Delicious things are all mine alone♪
まずいのや苦いのはルーナイト達に差し入れ！
Unpleasant or bitter things are care packages for Lunites!
チョコレートの噴水も キャンディの首飾りも
Chocolate fountains and candy necklaces,
素敵なのたくさんあるのら
there are so many wonderful things!
だからルーナのために集めてきてね♡
So gather them up for Luna♡
絶対絶対絶対約束♡ なのなのら！
Absolute, absolute, absolute promise♡ Nano na nora!
お料理だってお手のもの☆ みんなのハートも焦がすのよ♡
Even cooking is a breeze☆ We'll scorch everyone's hearts too♡
ナノリッシュだってパーフェクト☆ すぺしゃるなじーにあす！
Nanolish is also perfect☆ Special genius!
ゲームするのも好きだけど 怖いのは絶対イヤなのら……
I love playing games too, but being scared is an absolute no-no......
笑ったそこのルーナイト！ 後でお仕置きなのら♡
You there, Lunite, laughing! You'll be punished later♡
毎日楽しくて
Every day is so fun,
みんなで揃って 今日もまた大騒ぎ！
everyone getting together for another ruckus today!
あれもこれも遊ぶのら！ 楽しいのはひとりじめ♪
I want to play with this and that too! Fun things are all mine alone♪
怖いのはや痛いのは ルーナイト達にお任せ！
Leave scary or painful things to the Lunites!
お月様のブランコも 流れ星スライダーも
The moon swing and shooting star slider too,
楽しいのたくさんあるのら
there are so many fun things!
だから全然遊び足りてないのら！
That's why I'm nowhere near done playing!
まだまだまだまだまだまだ継続！ なのなのら！
Still continuing, still, still, still, still, still! Nano na nora!
なぁ…… Lunaの事ワガママワガママってイチイチうるさいのらね〜！
Jeez... Saying Luna is selfish, selfish and making a fuss every single time~!
ルーナは好きじゃない人にワガママは言わないのらよっ！
Luna doesn't say selfish things to people she doesn't like, you know!
それだけルーナイトの事頼りにしてるってことなのら！
That just means she relies on the Lunites that much!
だから……これからも先のルーナの事、守ってくれるのらよね？
So... from now on too, you'll protect Luna, right?
ほらね 着いてきて！ ルーナのナイトさま♡
See? Follow along! Luna's knight-sama♡
なーんてね♪
Just kidding♪
あれもこれも欲しいのら！ 全部全部欲しいのら！
I want this and that too! I want every single thing!
ルーナとルーナイトで たこ焼きパーティするのら！
Luna and the Lunites will have a takoyaki party!
もっともっと楽しい事 ずっとずっと嬉しい事
Even more fun things, always and forever happy things,
一緒に作っていけたならね きっとルーナとみんなの物語は
if we can create them together, I'm sure Luna and everyone's story
おとぎ話になっちゃうのかも！ プリンセスの願いをかなえて♡
might even turn into a fairy tale! Grant the princess's wish♡
絶対絶対絶対忠誠♡ なのなのら！ なのなのら！
Absolute, absolute, absolute loyalty♡ Nano na nora! Nano na nora!
ルーナイトへ♡ 早かったような、短かったような…あっという間の2年間だったのらね。ルーナイトはどう感じた？？いつもそばに居てくれて本当に本当にありがちゅ〜！！これからもルーナと一緒に前に進んでいこうね！！大好き♡ るーなのなのら♡
To my Lunites♡ It feels both fast and short... a fleeting 2 years, nanora. How did you feel?? Thank you so much, really, really, for always being by my side~~!! Let's keep moving forward together with Luna from now on too!! Love you♡ Luna nanora♡
ルーナイトへ♡
To my Lunatights ♡
早かったような、短かったような…あっという間の2年間だったのらね。
It feels both long and short... These past two years went by in a flash.
ルーナイトはどう感じた？？
How did you feel about it, Lunatights??
いつもそばに居てくれて本当に本当にありがちゅ～！！
Thank you so very, very much for always being by my side!!
これからもルーナイトと一緒に前に進んでいこうね！！
Let's keep moving forward together from now on, too!!
大好き♡ 姫森ルーナより
Love you so much ♡ From Himemori Luna
姫森ルーナ 2周年記念
Himemori Luna 2nd Anniversary